https://www.muellers.com/privacypolicy.dlp

PoolView All PoolCustom Pool CuesView All Custom Pool CuesDowney Custom CuesJacoby Custom CuesSanko Custom CuesProduction Pool CuesView All Production Pool CuesCuetec CuesLucasi CuesLucky CuesMcDermott CuesMeucci CuesMueller CuesPlayers CuesStar CuesStroker CuesViking CuesNFL Eliminator CuesHustler CuesJump CuesJump/Break CuesBreak Cues1-Piece House CuesNew CuesPerformance ShaftsView All Performance ShaftsPredator ShaftsPool Cue CasesView All Pool Cue Cases2x2 Cue Cases2x4 Cue Cases3x7 Cue CasesLeather Cue CasesSpecialty Cue CasesCue Racks & HoldersView All Cue Racks & HoldersFloor RacksWall RacksRack AccessoriesPortable Cue HoldersTalc HoldersPool BallsView All Pool BallsPool Ball SetsCue BallsAramith Replacement BallsBumper Pool BallsCarom BallsSnooker BallsTraining BallsNovelty Pool BallsPool Ball AccessoriesPool AccessoriesView All Pool AccessoriesChalkChalk HoldersTalcGlovesJoint ProtectorsPocket MarkersTipsView All TipsTraditional Leather Pressed TipsLayered Leather TipsPhenolic & Composite TipsScrew-On TipsSlip-On TipsCue Maintenance SuppliesView All Cue Maintenance SuppliesShaft MaintenanceTip MaintenanceCue Repair SuppliesView All Cue Repair SuppliesFerrulesTip PadsGlueBumpersWeight BoltsCollars & RingsJoint Pins & InsertsCue Lathes & Lathe AccessoriesPool Table ClothView All Pool Table ClothGorina Basalt ClothGorina A ClothGorina M ClothGorina Tournament 2000 ClothMueller's Rubber-Backed ClothMueller's Unbacked ClothPrecut ClothPool Table LightsView All Pool Table LightsPool Table LightsPool Table AccessoriesView All Pool Table AccessoriesPool Table CoversTriangles & RacksCone Talc & HoldersScore Markers & D-BoardsShake Bottle & PeasBridge Sticks, Heads, & HooksPool Table MaintenanceView All Pool Table MaintenancePlastic Pocket ComponentsRubber CushionsValley Coin-Op Table SuppliesHome Pool Table SuppliesRail Caps & Corner MitersRail Brushes & Cloth CleanersRail Repair SuppliesPool Table Recovery ToolsGlues & AdhesivesSpotsTraining AidsView All Training AidsPool Training Balls & DevicesBooks & DVDsView All Books & DVDsBooksDVDsClothingView All ClothingDead Stroke T-ShirtsPool & Billiard Embroidered ClothingPosters, Signs, & ClocksView All Posters, Signs, & ClocksPostersMetal SignsGifts & AccessoriesView All Gifts & AccessoriesPinsKeychainsDecalsHome & Office DecorTricks & GamesGifts
DartsView All DartsDartboardsView All DartboardsSoft Tip DartboardsSoft Tip DartsView All Soft Tip DartsB-Model Soft Tip DartsBottelsen Soft Tip DartsBullseye Soft Tip DartsClassic Brass Soft Tip DartsDead Stroke Soft Tip DartsHole-In-One Soft Tip DartsNemesis Soft Tip DartsPrism Soft Tip DartsSK Model Soft Tip DartsTight Grip Soft Tip DartsTraditional Brass Soft Tip DartsZombie Soft Tip DartsCustom-Designed Soft Tip DartsPlastic Soft Tip DartsSteel Tip DartsView All Steel Tip DartsBlack Knight Steel Tip DartsBottelsen Steel Tip DartsDead Stroke Steel Tip DartsExecutive Steel Tip DartsPlastic Steel Tip DartsDynastarView All DynastarDynastar FlightsPro Line Dart SystemsShaftsView All ShaftsAluminum ShaftsSpinning Aluminum ShaftsWire ShaftsPlastic ShaftsShaft Replacement Tops FlightsView All Flights2D/3D Slim Flights2D/3D Standard FlightsAmazon FlightsAmazon Cartoon FlightsBroken Glass FlightsCarbon FlightsCombat FlightsDelta FlightsDimplex Slim FlightsDimplex Standard FlightsDiva FlightsFantail FlightsHard Poly Slim FlightsHard Poly Standard Flightsi-FlightsKite/Pear FlightsMicro FlightsNylon Rib-Stock FlightsPentathlon Slim FlightsPentathlon Standard FlightsPoly Met FlightsPoly Pillar-Of-Light FlightsVignette FlightsVortex VX FlightsBudweiser® FlightsFlight Grab BagTips & Conversion PointsView All Tips & Conversion PointsSoft TipsSteel PointsDart CasesView All Dart CasesDart CasesDart AccessoriesView All Dart AccessoriesAdd-A-GramsFlight & Point ProtectorsToolsWaxes & RosinDartboard AccessoriesView All Dartboard AccessoriesScoreboardsAccessoriesBooks & ChartsView All Books & ChartsChartsGifts & AccessoriesView All Gifts & AccessoriesPinsPatchesDecalsDart Gifts & Kits
FoosballView All FoosballFoosballsDynamo Foosball PartsTornado Soccer Foosball PartsTournament Soccer Foosball Parts
ShuffleboardView All ShuffleboardShuffleboard PucksShuffleboard WaxShuffleboard Supplies
Table HockeyView All Table HockeyHandles & Pucks
Table TennisView All Table TennisPaddles & RacksTable Tennis Balls
Bumper PoolView All Bumper PoolBumper Pool BallsPosts & Replacement PartsBumper Pool Accessories
Game RoomView All Game RoomPokerGame Room SignsView All Game Room SignsMetal Game Room Signs
ApparelView All ApparelRT9 ClothingView All RT9 ClothingRT9 ClothingDead Stroke ClothingView All Dead Stroke ClothingDead Stroke T-ShirtsCloseouts
Professional Cue Repair
Previously Enjoyed Equipment
Privacy Policy
We care about your privacy
Mueller's Billiard & Dart Supplies has created this Privacy Policy to inform you about your personal information and how we use it.
Submitting Personal Information When you give us your personal information, we don't disclose it to any third parties except our authorized agents, who of course are bound to this policy. Mueller Recreational Products, Inc. will not sell, rent, or lease any of your information to others. We only use it to accurately process your order(s), send you a catalogue or other direct mail and/or email you our newsletter if you give us permission.
Ordering from www.muellers.com When you order from mueller's we need your name, email address, shipping address, and credit card number/expiration date. We only use this information to process your order(s), mail it (them) to your shipping address, and email order confirmations. If you agree to receive email from us, you will receive our newsletter every two weeks. You may unsubscribe from that at any time by clicking the link included or responding to the message. As previously mentioned in this private policy, we will not sell, rent, or lease any of your personal information to a third party.
Using Cookies Cookies are files stored on your computer's hard drive by your internet browser. Mueller's Billiard & Dart Supplies uses cookies as means of identifying our customers and tracking our methods of advertising. However, neither our authorized agents nor Mueller store any personally identifiable information in cookies or disclose it to a third party. We use information from these cookies to optimize our site in order to continue offering products like billiards, darts, and gaming supplies at great prices. When you leave our website, cookies allow us to hold your items in a shopping cart. After you return to muellers.com, your items will be saved in a shopping cart for your convenience.
Children's Online Privacy You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site.
Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personally identifiable information about visitors under 18 years of age.
If you are the parent or guardian of a minor under 18 years of age and believe that your child has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at info@muellers.com so that we may delete the minor's information.
Questions about Privacy Policy It's our goal for you to have a pleasant shopping experience at www.muellers.com. However, if you have any questions regarding this private policy, please email us at info@muellers.com.
We reserve the right to change this policy in the future. We recommend that you check this page on our website www.muellers.com regularly.
Recently Viewed
You don't have any recently viewed items.
Shopping history is enabled, turn off.
topTop
